just tell us a little bit about the type
of player Bills fans are going to see
when you step on the field.
>> You're going to get someone that's a
hard worker, is always trying to be
around the ball, um a leader, and
someone that you guys can count on for
years and years to come. Um you know,
I'm a player that I'm very passionate
about the game. Uh football is, you
know, all I do and I'm just ready to go
out there and compete at the highest
level.
when you made the decision to transfer,
what went into that decision and then
how do you think that helped you uh get
to the point where you are now?
>> I just wanted to be around, you know, a
community where, you know, they would
invest in me and I would be, you know,
in a spot where, um, you know, I just
felt welcomed and, um, able to, you
know, take my games to the next level.
Um, you know, I wanted to go somewhere
where it would be a higher standard and
the standard would be elevated and like
TC was the right spot.
>> All right. Thank you. Congrats,
>> sir.
>> Hey, Caleb. Katherine Fitzgerald from
the Buffalo News. Congratulations.
>> Thank you. I appreciate it.
>> Um, how would you describe your tackling
style? Just, you know, leading the team,
having so many. What is what goes into
tackling for you?
>> I take a lot of pride in tackling. You
know, as linebackers, you can't miss a
lot of tackles or that leads to, you
know, bad plays. So, for me, I always
just, you know, try and bring a lot of
force, a lot of power into my tackles.
uh striking with the near foot, near
shoulder, and always just finish on the
ball. Always trying to take the ball
away at all times and um always trying
to get the dudes down for minimal gains,
always knocking dudes back.
>> What was your process like with the
Bills throughout the draft process? Like
when did you talk to them? What was the
feeling like?
>> So, right after the draft, I came up for
a top 30 visit and I loved it. I love
Buffalo. I love the city. Got to meet
the whole staff. Everybody was warm and
welcome. And um this is this is my type
of spot for sure.
>> What did you love about the city?
>> I loved everything. I love how chill it
was. I love, you know, how the city just
pours everything they have into the team
and um I mean I love the facilities. Um
we went to some good food spots, so it
was it was a vibe for sure.
>> Awesome. Congrats again.
>> Thank you.
>> Mark Sports 1080. Congratulations.
>> Yes, sir. Thank you.
>> What was uh what was your reaction when
you finally got the call from Buffalo
and who did you share that moment with?
>> Uh so I'm just here with some friends.
Uh my parents, my grandparents, my
auntie and uncle, my siblings. Um and
you know, everyone was excited. Uh you
know, I'm excited. I'm just I'm ready to
go to work. Um that's that's all I do. I
have a very workmanlike mindset and I'm
just ready to to get after it and go
compete.
>> Absolutely. I mean, being a all 12 first
team selection and MVP in Alamobo, um,
what what what part of it as far as
handling coverage, communication, and
run fits, how how much of that does that
fit your profile?
>> It definitely fits my profile. You know,
I I pride myself on the versatility of
my game. Um, just being able to be a
three-phase complete linebacker, you
know, stop the run, stop the pass, and
affect the quarterback. And I feel like
I can bring all three of those to the
city for sure.
>> Now, uh, you know, is this more of a
defensive draft? Bills have selected TJ
Parker. Uh they selected IGB. What is
going to be like, you know, being part
of that class and getting an opportunity
to play with those guys?
>> Yes, sir. I'm excited to meet those guys
and like I said, just get to work. I'm
excited to, you know, give Buffalo 110%
everything I do and just just get after
it for sure.
>> Appreciate your time, man. Congrats.
>> Yes, sir. Thank you.